[Music]
[音乐]
我将向您展示如何制作
I'm going to show you how to make an
天使圣诞贺卡和我展示之前
你如何制作这个，我会展示
I'm going to show you how to make an
angel Christmas cards and before I show
你几本书以及其他
人们已经解决了这个问题
angel Christmas cards and before I show
you how to make this one I'll just show
排名第一的Chuck有天使
菲舍尔，实际上他有很多
you how to make this one I'll just show
you a couple of books with how other
他们中的天使，但不是我意思是他们
确实有一些3D机翼，但它们相当
you a couple of books with how other
people have dealt with the subject so
一路穿过天使
他们很小，不是超级超级
people have dealt with the subject so
number one we've got angels by Chuck
类似于第一个面包的3d
无论如何相当有趣
number one we've got angels by Chuck
Fischer and actually he has a lot of
主题，这就是查克·菲舍尔（Chuck Fischer）的
天使另外两本书都是
Fischer and actually he has a lot of
angels in them but not I mean these they
罗伯茨·布达所以有十二天
圣诞节的到来
angels in them but not I mean these they
do have some 3d wings but they're fairly
基于扭曲的天使数组
机制是教程十七
do have some 3d wings but they're fairly
all the way through there's angels but
那就是那个另一个
罗伯茨·奥布达（Robertsóbuda）的作品是
all the way through there's angels but
they're quite small and not super super
圣诞字母，这是为
天使，这是一个很好奇的设计
they're quite small and not super super
3d that's similar to the first bread
在那里完成它是基于v折
然后作为水上飞机和一个槽
anyway quite quite an interesting
所以现在我将向您展示如何制作
一个，就在我们进入它之前
anyway quite quite an interesting
subject and that's Chuck Fischer's
告诉你如何装饰翅膀
这是我之前做的另一张卡片
subject and that's Chuck Fischer's
angels the other two books are both by
是一张鸟卡，你可以看到那只鸟，但是
忽略那只鸟
angels the other two books are both by
Roberts óbuda so there's the twelve days
看着机翼的完成方式
然后装饰翅膀的方式
Roberts óbuda so there's the twelve days
of Christmas and here we've got a whole
它具有三种不同的色调
黄牌，切成这些形状
of Christmas and here we've got a whole
array of angels based on the twisting
我只是认为这确实有效
很好，这个天使实际上是基于
array of angels based on the twisting
mechanism which is tutorial seventeen
如果你从下面看这个
最后，您会看到它是漂浮的
mechanism which is tutorial seventeen
and that's that one the other one also
浮动飞机是教程
十二，然后这些是头
and that's that one the other one also
by Roberts óbuda is this one the
头是尖的V型折
稍微倾斜使其成为重点
by Roberts óbuda is this one the
Christmas alphabet and this a is for
虽然它被切断，然后
小号通过插槽上的位置固定
Christmas alphabet and this a is for
angel it's quite a curious design he's
手和头上的插槽
保留了小号搜索
angel it's quite a curious design he's
done there it is based on a v-fold and
这些是您开始的作品
当然，将基片彻底折叠
done there it is based on a v-fold and
then as a floating plane and a slot
然后做水上飞机
这是一块，有三个平行
so now I'll show you how to make this
折痕将其切成三个，所以三个
或多或少甚至块，然后你采取
so now I'll show you how to make this
one and just before we go into it I'll
其中最大的一个是
会像这样粘在脊椎上
one and just before we go into it I'll
show you how the wings can be decorated
你想要这个陡峭的地方
形状越坚硬
show you how the wings can be decorated
this is another card I made before this
在下面并不重要
选项卡走哪条路，但我要去
this is another card I made before this
is a bird card you can see the bird but
让他们伸出来，这样我就可以保持
中央山脊真的很紧密地进入了
is a bird card you can see the bird but
ignore the bird it's just actually
脊椎，所以我会在上面放些胶水
在那边我会坚持下去
ignore the bird it's just actually
looking at the way the wings are done
只有你知道，也许只有一半
距离脊柱一厘米
looking at the way the wings are done
and the way the wings are decorated then
另一个标签上的胶粘到周围
[音乐]
and the way the wings are decorated then
it's with three different tones of
关闭可以在哪里找到的基地
想粘下来，那是
it's with three different tones of
yellow card and cut into these shapes
它的开始是并行错误
另外两块用来
yellow card and cut into these shapes
and I just think that works really
每边平行四边形，所以放胶
在那一次，这一次你坚持
and I just think that works really
nicely this angel is actually based on
折痕
绝对与那里的山脊齐平
nicely this angel is actually based on
this if you look at it underneath from
最重要的是一个
现在你把它折起来
this if you look at it underneath from
end on you'll see that it is a floating
将胶水放在另一个标签上
现在将其关闭，以便进入
end on you'll see that it is a floating
plane the floating plane is tutorial
它的关闭位置将其关闭，以便找到
它要坚持下去的地方
plane the floating plane is tutorial
twelve and then these are the head the
另一边的另一边
绝对与山脊齐平
twelve and then these are the head the
head is a pointed v-fold it's just
顶部，然后将胶水粘在另一个标签上
涂抹周围然后关闭
head is a pointed v-fold it's just
slightly angled to make it a point and
所以这是你的基本水上飞机
这样看就可以看到
slightly angled to make it a point and
though it's being cut off and then the
中间有平行的折痕
然后在每边平行四边形
though it's being cut off and then the
trumpet is held in place by slots on the
在页面上方创建这两个平面
他们都与此页面平行
trumpet is held in place by slots on the
hand and a slot on the head
是天使的主体需要
在折痕中间向下折痕
hand and a slot on the head
that holds the trumpet search that's out
我将要进入沟壑
使它对称但不需要
these are the pieces you start with the
成为你可能会选择两者
翅膀在不同的位置真的
these are the pieces you start with the
base sheet of course thoroughly fold it
没关系，他们只是去
贴在这两个平面上
base sheet of course thoroughly fold it
and then to make the floating plane
在您进行设计时，取决于您
只是玩弄它，我们可以坚持
and then to make the floating plane
here's a piece it's got three parallel
这一切都在同一时间，
胶粘在两个表面上，重要的
here's a piece it's got three parallel
creases cut it into three so the three
要做的是确保此折痕
进入那个同花顺
creases cut it into three so the three
more or less even chunks then you take
沟壑在那里，我们将其关闭到
确保一切
more or less even chunks then you take
the biggest one of these and this is
安全的声音，这就是主体
这就是你可以剪的头
the biggest one of these and this is
gonna stick over the spine like this and
在个人资料中看到的形状
你想要头部的轮廓是
gonna stick over the spine like this and
you want this very steep the steeper it
您在每一侧添加一个标签，然后
这里有一个小槽可以
you want this very steep the steeper it
is the more rigid the shape it's all
握住小号，以便小号可以走
在里面，被困在两侧，如果
is the more rigid the shape it's all
underneath it doesn't really matter
你这样看就可以看到
小号经过那不是然后
underneath it doesn't really matter
which way the tabs go but I'm going to
手中实际上有插槽
好，这样就可以吹小号了
which way the tabs go but I'm going to
have them sticking out so I can keep the
直接从页面突出
坚持这取决于你真的你
have them sticking out so I can keep the
central Ridge really closely into the
知道你把它放高还是低
在大约一半的地方
central Ridge really closely into the
spine so I'll put a bit of glue on that
给你这个设计，所以我再次把
胶在一侧可以平整或
spine so I'll put a bit of glue on that
side there I'll stick that down it's
如你所愿，我会坚持下去
在那里，然后我将胶水涂在
side there I'll stick that down it's
only you know maybe even only half a
另一边并关闭它
关闭它，这样就可以进入
only you know maybe even only half a
centimeter from the spine and some more
现在放置武器，以便您可以看到
武器，如果你看着它
centimeter from the spine and some more
glue on the other tab smear it around
这样一来，您将看到一折
这里，这里有一个缺点，这两个方面
glue on the other tab smear it around
[Music]
是平行的，然后我切出形状
用胳膊肘来做
[Music]
close the base that can find where it
手臂掉下来，再次上升到
持有人再次跳过去
close the base that can find where it
wants to glue down so that's the
折成两半并对称地切割
所以当你打开它给你这个
wants to glue down so that's the
beginning of it that's a parallel fault
形状，因此这些标签将进入
在它们下面
beginning of it that's a parallel fault
the other two pieces are used to make
这样的事情，所以这实际上是
您想思考的平行折叠
the other two pieces are used to make
parallelograms on each side so put glue
关于小号在哪里直行
会是这样，所以你需要两个
parallelograms on each side so put glue
on that and this time you stick the the
插槽彼此对齐
再说一次，我要坚持下去
on that and this time you stick the the
crease
一侧大约在肩膀上
大概就是正确的
crease
absolutely flush with there the ridge on
与此折痕平行粘合
主体，然后我们将胶水涂在
absolutely flush with there the ridge on
the top of that so there's that one and
另一边并关闭
这是小号，只有一个
the top of that so there's that one and
now you fold it up into its closed
最后一点折痕
那里一个很小的标签
now you fold it up into its closed
position put the glue on the other tab
那就是要坚持的东西
像这样去的地方
and now close it down so it goes into
穿过我手中的插槽，
通过填充线，那就是
and now close it down so it goes into
its closed position close it so it finds
会像那样粘在里面，所以我会
只是在上面放一点胶
its closed position close it so it finds
where it wants to stick down put the
蜘蛛约克会得到它吗
在脑海里，我实际上
where it wants to stick down put the
other one on the other side
用笔之类的东西来压它
靠在头上
absolutely flush with the Ridge on the
确保它确定我坚持很好
好吧，我想现在知道了，我只是
absolutely flush with the Ridge on the
top and put glue on the other tab well
将其关闭以鼓励其坚持
听起来这就是圣诞节的天使
top and put glue on the other tab well
smear it around and then close it down
卡天使在那里吹小号
我们是
so this is the basic floating plane you
[音乐]
[掌声]
so this is the basic floating plane you
look at it that way on you can see
您
[音乐]
look at it that way on you can see
there's a parallel fold in the middle